excuse me for disturbing you
Yes, please.
Cheers!
Thank you very much.
What I want to ask you is...
What should we do about education?
Feb.
During the recording
I sometimes say things like greetings
When I was a teenager
When I was a teenager, I had a manager who was like a mother to me.
like a mother.
She was like a mother to me all the time.
Greetings, lady
Smile, One.
You can't say it yourself
Even though I'm such an oddball
I can't teach you how to be a human being
I can't do it.
Because...
She's a Janko, isn't she?
She's the type of girl who says, "You're a Yanko, aren't you?
Especially girls who become idols.
They have a lot of individuality, don't they?
That's why I have to adapt to them.
What's the best word
What words they want the most
and what they want to hear the most.
I learned it at AVT.
That's why
All the words are
You're so kind.
I'm sure no one feels bad when interacting with you.
I don't feel bad when I'm in contact with you.
And people who are anxious
I felt your power
I felt it so much.
This is what I've been carrying on my back
I felt that this is the human power of the people
I felt that this is the human power of the person
I really felt it.
It's amazing.
What about your style?
What do you mean?
I don't like it.
She's such a big deal.
I'd hate to have a junior.
I think you look great just the way you are.
Senpai
Janko.
Janko senior
Janko senior.
Janko's senior is here.
That's for sure.
After the first set.
I felt good.
It's not often that you get it right.
Not too many, right?
There's the intense alignment.
and the feeling of being in shape
If you look at the ratio
I would say that there are relatively few
Right?
It's happening so fast.
It would be nice if you had feelings.
That's about it.
I use it as a mental reset.
If I don't go, I can't be nice to people.
How did you live before that?
How did you live like that?
I had a lot of anger issues.
I never cut the bubbles.
It gets wet.
I've changed since the thernalist.
Is that how you felt when you first met her?
You really felt like you had a chance to meet her?
Yeah.
I'm, uh, starting with a reconnaissance of the facility.
You won't?
I will.
Check the flow lines.
Whatever the temperature.
I can do that.
About mid-height and full height
Pipes
I wanted to be able to work with any set
I wanted to be able to go
I dared to put myself in
A lukewarm sauna room
Tepid water bath
I went to the water bath
Before I didn't want to be here
I can go to the water bath before I don't want to be here.
I don't know how long I can stay in there.
On the contrary.
I can stay in there forever.
It's a little bit of heaven.
Isn't that the best?
I thought...
What?
It's so relaxing.
You can't stay in there forever.
You can't go in all the time.
I thought it could be fun.